Today I came to the terrace to make a reel, then
why did our neighbours start getting jealous?   Yes
, today I also have to shoot this reel.
For this, I took out a beautiful saree from the bed
and wore this blouse.
But before that I tied my hair
which does not suit the saree.  It took
me 10-12 minutes just to tie the saree.
Then she quickly came and said that she
would make the reel on the terrace in such hot sun.  You will become even darker.
I said don't worry about me.
Because I am from M to PM.  I try the routine.
Meaning,
I use it first thing in the morning.  Thermode's Purple
Sunscreen that protects the skin from UV rays
and gives instant glow.  It is also light
weight and non-greasy, which is
best for oily skin.  And by looking at the reviews you
can know that this has
become not only my first choice but the first choice of many other people also.
And at night I use Derm's
2% Kojic Acid Night Cream.
Reduces dark spots and pigmentation and
gives a glossy glow thanks to the
goodness of kojic acid, neem and alpha arginine.  And look how much glow is there on my face even after making the reel.
If you also
want this product then it
is available at a high discount on perp.com.  Tagged above.
You can order it by clicking here